http://blakeshelton.com/privacy-policy#adchoices

LAST UPDATED: MAY 22, 2018
Warner Music Nashville (“Company”), a Warner Music Group company, is concerned about privacy
issues and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information. This Privacy Policy
describes our practices in
connection with information that we or our third-party service providers collect through certain of our
owned or controlled websites, web properties (e.g., widgets and applications) and mobile applications
(“Mobile Apps”)
in each case, that link to this Privacy Policy (each, a “Property” or collectively the
“Properties”). By providing Personal Information (as defined below) to us through the
Properties, you agree to the terms
and conditions of this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other
practices of any third party, including Facebook, Inc., Apple Inc., Google LLC, Microsoft Corp., any
wireless carriers, our artists, our affiliates
and any third party operating any site or property to which any Property contains a link. In addition, the
inclusion of a link on any Property does not imply endorsement of, or affiliation with, the linked site or
Property by us or by our
artists or affiliates. Please note that the Properties may include the ability to access and submit
(including, for example, via a third-party software application or service that is available through or in
connection with a Property) certain
information directly to third parties, such as Facebook, or to any application platform, such as Apple’s App
Store or Google Play. Such information is submitted by you directly to such third parties and this Privacy
Policy does not apply to
any such information submitted by you.
Your California Privacy Rights: If you are a California resident, you may request certain
information once per year about our disclosure of certain categories of Personal Information during the
preceding calendar year to third
parties for such third parties’ own direct marketing purposes. Please send your request by email to privacypolicy@wmg.com, or by postal mail to Warner Music Group,
Attn: Privacy Coordinator, 1633
Broadway, New York, NY 10019. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the
email or mailing addresses specified in this section.
PERSONAL INFORMATION
Personal Information We Collect
Two types of information are collected in connection with the Properties: Personal Information and Other
Information. “Personal Information” is information that identifies you or makes you
identifiable as an individual. “Other Information”
is any information that does not reveal your specific identity. If we are required to treat Other
Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then we may use and disclose it for the purposes
for which we use and disclose Personal
Information as detailed in this Policy. Other Information is addressed separately below, under the heading
“OTHER INFORMATION”.
We and our third-party service providers may collect the following Personal Information from you:
Name
Postal address (including billing and shipping addresses)
Telephone number
Email address
Credit and debit card number
Shopping Cart Content
Collection of Personal Information
We and our third-party service providers collect Personal Information through the Properties in a variety of
ways, including:
Through the Properties
We may collect Personal Information through the Properties, for example, when you register for
newsletters or other communications through the Properties, make a purchase or make a request.
Offline
We may collect Personal Information from you offline, e.g., if you provide information to us at
a concert venue.
From Other Sources
We may receive your Personal Information from other sources, for example:
publicly available databases; or
marketing partners when they share information with us in the context of marketing and
promotional campaigns related to our business.
If you use your social media or other third party account to enter our sweepstakes, contest, or
promotions or via an initiation to sign into such account on our Properties, you will share
certain Personal Information from your third
party account with us which may include, for example, your name, email address, photo, list of
social media contacts, listening history, favorite tracks and any other information that you
make or which is otherwise accessible to
us when you connect through such third party account.
You are not required by statute or contract to provide any Personal Information to us.  For example,
when you participate in various opportunities provided through the Properties, we collect Personal
Information from you in order to enable
you (or us) to complete your experience on the Properties.
How We May Use Personal Information
We and our third-party service providers may use Personal Information for the following business purposes
including:
Providing the functionality of the Properties and fulfilling your requests.
To provide the Properties’ functionality to you, such as arranging access to your registered
account, and providing you with related customer service.
To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, when you contact us via one of our
online contact forms or otherwise, for example, when you send us questions, suggestions,
compliments or complaints, or when you request information
about our Properties.
To send to you administrative information, including information regarding the Properties and
changes to our terms, conditions and policies.
To complete and fulfill your purchase, for example, to process your payments, have your order
delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related
customer service.
To allow you to send messages (for example, music clips or artist information) to a friend
through the Properties. By using such functionality, you are telling us that you are entitled to
use and provide us with your friend’s name
and email address.
We will engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you and/or to comply with a
legal obligation.
Providing you with our newsletter and/or other marketing materials and facilitating social
sharing
To send you marketing communications, that we believe may be of interest to you if you have
indicated that you would like to receive them (including, without limitation, by our third-party
service providers that send direct mail, email,
and other types of advertising)
To send you SMS text messages using your telephone number, e.g., if you participated in a
sweepstake with this number and you have indicated you would like to receive them. Please keep
in mind that message and data rates may apply.
You should check with your mobile service provider for applicable data rates. At any time, you
may text back “HELP” for further information regarding text messages. If additional rules are
provided in connection with any specific
SMS text message sign-ups, such rules shall also apply and shall control in the event that they
conflict with this Privacy Policy.
To facilitate social sharing functionality that you choose to use.
We will engage in this activity with your consent.
Analysis of Personal Information for business reporting and providing personalized
services.
To analyze or predict our users’ preferences in order to prepare aggregated trend reports on how
our digital content is used, so we can improve our Properties.
To personalize your experience on the Properties using your IP address, by presenting content,
products, and offers tailored to you.
We will provide personalized services either with your consent or because we have a legitimate interest.
Allowing you to participate in sweepstakes, contests or other promotions.
To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions using your email
address, and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules,
which could contain additional information about
how we use and disclose your Personal Information, so we suggest that you read these rules
carefully; in the event of a conflict between such rules and this Privacy Policy, such rules
will govern.
We use this information to manage our contractual relationship with you.
Aggregating and/or anonymizing Personal Information.
We may aggregate and/or anonymize Personal Information so that it will no longer be considered
Personal Information. We do so to generate other data for our use, which we may use and disclose
for any purpose.
We will engage in this activity because we have a legitimate interest.
Accomplishing our business purposes.
Data analysis, for example, to improve the efficiency of our Properties;
Audits, to verify that our internal processes function as intended and are compliant with legal,
regulatory or contractual requirements;
For fraud and security monitoring purposes, for example, to detect and prevent cyberattacks or
attempts to commit identity theft;
For developing new products and services;
For enhancing, improving, or modifying our current products and services;
For identifying usage trends, for example, understanding which parts of our Properties are of
most interest to users;
For determining the effectiveness of promotional campaigns, so that we can adapt our campaigns
to the needs and interests of our users; and
For operating and expanding our business activities, for example, understanding which parts of
our Properties are of most interest to our users so we can focus our energies on meeting our
users’ interests.
We engage in these activities to manage our contractual relationship with you, to comply with a legal
obligation, and/or because we have a legitimate interest.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We may disclose Personal Information:
To our affiliates for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.
You can consult the list and location of our affiliates here http://wminewmedia.com/affiliates/.
Warner Music Inc. is the party responsible for the management of jointly-used Personal
Information.
To our third-party service providers (and in some cases, our affiliates), to
facilitate the services they provide to us
These can include providers of services such as hosting, data analysis, payment processing,
order fulfillment, infrastructure provision, IT services, customer service, email delivery,
credit card processing, auditing and other similar
services to enable them to provide such services.
To third parties, to permit them to send you marketing
communications, consistent with your choices.
Unaffiliated third parties or their vendors, to permit them to send, or cause to be sent,
marketing communications to you in online and offline media.
Our artists (including any of the artists’ band members, if applicable) and their
representatives, so that the artists and their representatives may use this information to send
to you communications (including marketing communications)
that they believe may be of interest to you, including, for example, if you (a) sign up to join
the applicable artist’s mailing list and/or to receive such artist’s newsletters, (b) register
with the applicable artist’s website,
or (c) have otherwise indicated that you would like to receive information and/or marketing
communications from the applicable artist. We do not control, and are not responsible for,
artists’ and their representatives’ use of Personal
Information.
To a relevant artist who is no longer affiliated with us, if you indicated an interest in such
artist (for example, by registering with the artist’s website)
To third parties that sponsor contests, sweepstakes and similar promotions so that they can
facilitate and administer such contests, sweepstakes and promotions
By using the Properties, you may elect to disclose Personal Information
On or through message boards, chat, profile pages and blogs and other services to which you are
able to post information and materials. Please note that any information and materials that you
post or disclose on or through a Property
will become public information, and may be available to visitors to such Property and to the
general public, and may be redistributed through the Internet and other media channels where
they will reach an even broader audience.
Additionally, please note that, per our Terms of Use located at http://www.warnermusicnashville.com/terms-of-use,
we retain certain rights in the information and materials
that you post on or through the Properties, and we may use and disclose such information and
materials (including any Personal Information included therein) in accordance with our Terms of
Use. We urge you to be very careful when
deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any Other Information, on or through the
Properties. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE USE OR DISCLOSURE OF ANY INFORMATION YOU VOLUNTARILY
DISCLOSE THROUGH ANY PROPERTY.
Other Uses and Disclosures
We may also use and disclose your Personal Information as necessary or appropriate, especially when we have a
legal obligation or legitimate interest to do so:
To comply with applicable law.
This can include laws outside your country of residence.
To respond to requests from public and government authorities.
These can include authorities outside your country of residence.
To cooperate with law enforcement.
For example, when we respond to law enforcement requests and orders.
For other legal reasons.
To enforce our terms and conditions
To protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates or artists;
To protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, or that of our affiliates, our artists, you
or others; or
To allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
In connection with a sale or business transaction.
We have a legitimate interest in disclosing or transferring your Personal Information to a third
party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or
other disposition of all or any portion
of our business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar
proceedings) Such third parties may include, for example, an acquiring entity and its
advisors.
Retention Period
We will retain your Personal Information for as long as needed or permitted in light of the purpose(s) for
which it was obtained and consistent with applicable law.
The criteria we use to determine our retention periods include:
The length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you and provide the Properties to you (for
example, for as long as you have an account with us or keep using the Properties);
Whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject (for example, certain laws require us to
keep records of your transactions for a certain period of time before we can delete them); or
Whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes
of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).
Sensitive Information
We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose to us, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social
security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other
beliefs, health, criminal background
or trade union membership) on or through the Properties or otherwise.
OTHER INFORMATION
Other Information We May Collect
We and our third-party service providers may collect Other Information (defined above) such as:
Browser and device information
Mobile App usage data
Server log files
Information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies. If you are located within the
EEA please read our cookie policy http://www.wminewmedia.com/cookies/ for
further details on our use of cookies.
Geographic location information
Demographic information and other non-personally identifiable information provided by you
Information about how you use the Properties
Aggregated information
How We May Collect Other Information
We and our third-party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including:
Through your browser or your device: Certain information is collected by most
browsers, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, device type (Windows or Macintosh), screen
resolution, operating system version,
Internet browser type and version and the type and version of a Property that you are using. We and our
service providers may also collect a unique device identifier assigned by us or our service providers to
the device from which you
are accessing a Property and other transactional information for the device that we and our service
providers may use to serve content and advertisements to the device.
Through your use of Mobile Apps: When you download and use a Mobile App, we and
our service providers may track and collect Mobile App usage data, such as the date and time the Mobile
App on your device accesses our servers
and what information and files have been downloaded to the Mobile App based on your device number.
Through server log files: An Internet Protocol (IP) address is a number that is
automatically assigned to your device from which you are accessing a Property by your Internet Service
Provider (ISP), and is identified
and logged automatically in our server log files whenever you visit the Property, along with the time of
the visit and the activity on the Property. We and our service providers use IP addresses for purposes
such as calculating Property
usage levels, helping diagnose server problems, administering the Properties and determining your
approximate geographic location.
Using cookies: We and our service providers may use cookies, pixel
tags, web beacons, Adobe Flash technology (including Flash Local Stored Objects (“Flash
LSOs”)) and other similar technologies to, among
other things, better serve you with more tailored information for our products and services, and for
those of third parties, facilitate your ongoing access to and use of the Properties, and collect and
store information about your use
of the Properties. For example, pixel tags and web beacons may be used in connection with a Property to,
among other things, track the actions of such Property’s users, measure the success of marketing
campaigns and compile statistics
about such Property’s usage and response rates.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure
on most devices through which the Properties are accessed that allows you to decline the use of
cookies. To learn more about cookies,
please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. If you choose to decline cookies, then
some or all of the features, functionality and promotions available through
the Properties may not be available to you.
If your device stores Flash LSOs, and if you do not want Flash LSOs stored on your device
through which you access the Properties, you can adjust the settings of your Flash player to
block Flash LSO storage using the tools contained
using the Website Storage Settings Panel. You can also control Flash LSOs by going
to the Global Storage Settings Panel and following the instructions (which
may include instructions that explain, for example, how to delete existing Flash LSOs (referred
to as “information” on the Macromedia
site), how to prevent Flash LSOs from being placed on your device without you being asked, and
(for Flash Player 8 and later) how to block Flash LSOs that are not being delivered by the
operator of the page you are on at the time).
Please note that setting the Flash Player to restrict or limit acceptance of Flash LSOs may
reduce or impede the functionality of some Flash applications, including, potentially, Flash
applications used in connection with the Properties
or our content. We expect our service providers and technology suppliers to honor any decision
by you to restrict or limit Flash LSOs, but we cannot guarantee that they will do so.
The use of these technologies allows our vendors, and third parties and their vendors, to
deliver advertisements about our products and services, and the products and services of others,
when you use the Properties or other applications
or visit websites or web properties across the Internet on any of your devices. These parties
may place so-called “pixel tags,” “web beacons,” “clear GIFs” or similar technologies on the
device through which you access the Properties,
and other applications or websites across the Internet, and also place or recognize third-party
cookies when you use the Properties, or other applications, websites or web properties. They may
also use these technologies, along
with information they collect about your online use, to recognize you across the devices you
use, such as a mobile device and a laptop. These vendors and third parties may use information
about your visits, on the different devices
you use, to the Properties, and other applications, websites or web properties (excluding your
name, address, and telephone number), as well as information received from third parties, to
provide advertisements for us and others
about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information
about this practice, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org or
the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info.  You may also visit those sites to opt out of
these advertising practices in desktop and mobile browsers on the
particular device on which you are accessing this Privacy Policy.
Our Properties do not respond to browser-based do-not-track signals.
Geographic location information: If you use any location-enabled products or services,
you may be sending us location information. When you use a location-enabled service, we may collect and
process information about your
precise geographical location, such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device. We and our third party service
providers and partners may use your device’s physical location to provide you with personalized
location-based services, content and
advertisements. In some instances, you may be permitted to allow or deny such uses of your device’s
location, but if you choose to deny such uses, we may not be able to provide you with the applicable
personalized services and content.
From you: We may collect demographic information, such as your zip code or gender, as
well as other information, such as your preferred means of communication, when you voluntarily provide this
information to us. This information
does not necessarily personally identify you or any other user of the Properties, unless further information
is added to it that would allow identification to take place. In such case, the information will be treated
as Personal Information.
Information about how you interact on the Properties: We may collect information about
how you interact on the Properties. For example, some Properties may utilize analytic tools to help us
better serve you through improved
products, services, and revisions to the Properties. This collected information may let us know which
services and features you are using the most within a Property, as well as device type and hardware
features, country and language of download,
etc.
By aggregating information: We may aggregate Personal Information so that the
end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the Properties, for example, by using
Personal Information to calculate the percentage
of our users who like a particular artist.
How We May Use and Disclose Other Information
Please note that we may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to
do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information
under applicable law, then we
may use it as described in “How We May Collect Other Information” section above, as well as for all the
purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. In some instances, we may combine Other
Information with Personal Information
(such as combining your name with your geographical location). If we combine any Other Information with
Personal Information, the combined information will be treated by us as Personal Information as long as it
is combined.
SECURITY
We will use reasonable physical, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information under
our control. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please notify
us immediately in accordance
with the “Contacting Us” section below.
CHOICES AND ACCESS
Your choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information
We give you many choices regarding our use and disclosure of Personal Information about you for marketing
purposes.
You may opt-out from the following as set forth below:
Receiving marketing-related emails from us and our affiliates: If you do not want
to receive marketing-related emails from us and our affiliates on a going-forward basis, you may opt-out
from receiving such emails either
by using the unsubscribe mechanism provided in the email or by emailing us at  privacypolicy@wmg.com.
Receiving marketing-related SMS text messages from us and our affiliates: If you
do not want to receive marketing-related SMS text messages from us and our affiliates on a going-forward
basis, you may opt-out from receiving
such messages by texting back “STOP” or by emailing us at  privacypolicy@wmg.com.
Our sharing of your Personal Information with artists or unaffiliated third parties for their
marketing purposes: If you prefer that we not share your Personal Information on a
going-forward basis with artists or unaffiliated
third parties for their marketing purposes, you may opt-out from such sharing by emailing us at  privacypolicy@wmg.com.
In each case, please make clear in your email what you are opting-out from. We will comply with your
request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that, if you do opt-out from receiving
marketing-related messages from us, we may still
send administrative messages to you.
How you can access, change or delete your Personal Information
If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, restrict or delete Personal Information that
you previously provided to us, if you would like to object to our use of your Personal Information, or if
you would like to request to
receive an electronic copy of your Personal Information for purposes of transmitting it to another company
(to the extent this right to data portability is provided to you by applicable law), you may contact us
at:  privacypolicy@wmg.com.
We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.
In your request, please make clear what Personal Information you would like to have changed, whether you
would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what
limitations you would like to put
on our use of your Personal Information.  For your protection, we may only implement requests with
respect to the Personal Information associated with the particular email address that you use to send us
your request, and we may need
to verify your identity before implementing your request.  We will try to comply with your request as
soon as reasonably practicable.
Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any
transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion (e.g., when you make a purchase or
enter a promotion, you may not
be able to change or delete the Personal Information provided until after the completion of such purchase or
promotion).
Where our collection and use of Personal Information is based on your consent, you may withdraw such consent
at any time by emailing us at privacypolicy@wmg.com, and such
withdrawal will not affect the
lawfulness of processing based on consent before your withdrawal.
Cross-Border Transfer
The Properties are controlled and operated from the United States; accordingly, this Privacy Policy, and our
collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information, is governed by the laws of the United States,
and the Properties are not
intended to subject Company or any of its affiliates to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or
territory other than that of the United States. Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any
country where we have facilities
or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Properties you understand that your information
will be transferred to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which
may have data protection rules
that are different from those of your country.
If you are located in the EEA: Some of the non-EEA countries are recognized by the European
Commission as providing an adequate level of data protection according to EEA standards (the full list of
these countries is available
here). For transfers from the EEA to countries not considered adequate by
the European Commission, we have put in place adequate measures, such as standard contractual clauses
adopted by the European Commission regarding Personal Information. You may obtain a copy of these measures
by contacting privacypolicy@wmg.com or consult standard terms by
following this link.
The Properties are not directed to individuals under the age of thirteen (13), and we request that such
individuals do not provide Personal Information through the Properties.
UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please take a look at the “LAST UPDATED” legend at
the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy
will become effective when we
make the revised Privacy Policy available on or through a Property.
CONTACTING US
Warner Music Group, located at 1633 Broadway, New York, NY 10019, is the company responsible for collection,
use and disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our data processing practices, please
contact us by email at  privacypolicy@wmg.com.
Alternatively, if you are located within the
EU/EEA, you may also lodge a complaint with a data protection authority for your country or region, or where
an alleged infringement of applicable data protection law occurs. A list of data protection authorities is
available here.
We are located at the following address:
Warner Music Group
Legal Department
1633 Broadway
New York, NY 10019
Attn: Privacy Coordinator
Please note that email communications are not always secure, so please do not include credit card information
or other sensitive information in your email messages to us.
x
Subscribe to WMN’s e-mail list for latest updates, tour announcements, new music and more.
terms
By submitting my information, I agree to receive personalized updates and marketing messages about Warner Music Nashville, based on my information, interests, activities, website visits and device data and in accordance with the Privacy Policy. I understand that I can opt-out at any time by emailing privacypolicy@wmg.com.
Thank you!
Thank you
for subscribing. For customized updates, enter zipcode and birthday
birthday
MM
01
02
03
04
05
06
31
Subscribe to additional WMN artists below (optional):
terms
By submitting my information, I agree to receive personalized updates and marketing messages about Warner Music Nashville based on my information, interests, activities, website visits and device data and in accordance with the
Privacy Policy. In addition, if I have checked the box above, I agree to receive such updates and messages about similar artists,
products and offers. I understand that I can opt-out from messages at any time by emailing
privacypolicy@wmg.com.
